--== 本影片由 CMCT 团队 荣誉出品 ==--
更多精彩影视 请访问 http://cmct.tv
影片压制｜呆呆　　字幕制作｜呆呆
招募Q群｜324446465
字幕转制｜天外生物
感谢原字幕制作者
这是一个关于过去…
This is a story of the past...
和未来的故事
and the future.
我们将走向未来 但首先 我们会经历过去
We will come to the future, but first, the past.
这是沃里克伯爵
Here we have the Earl of Warwick.
从他的表情可以看出
We can see by his petulantly arched brow...
他肯定不是在干好事情
that he is not enroute to a good deed.
来吧
Obey!
魔法
Enchanted...
你还想活吗 老巫婆？
Do you wish to live, old witch?
你已经违背了王国的法律
You have committed grave crimes...
违背了上帝和国王
against God and your king, have you not?
- 饶恕我吧  - 安静
- Have mercy, my lord.  - Silence.
那个法国人 康德·瑟伯特
The Frenchman Count Thibault of Malfete...
将要娶国王的女儿 罗莎琳德公主
shall wed Lady Rosalind, the daughter of our king.
我要那个女人
I desire that woman.
我要得到那个女人
I alone am fit to take her hand.
还有她的城堡 她的土地和财产…
And her castle, lands, the riches that are her dowry.
你还不笨啊 老巫婆
Thou art not as stupid as thou art hideous, old hag.
明天晚上
Tomorrow night...
国王将会盛情款待康德
the king shall feast the arrival of the count.
在宴会结束前 我要他永远在我眼前消失
I want the count dead before the feast is over.
这儿有一小袋金子
A small fortune in gold...
是给替我办事的人预备的
awaits the sorceress who doth my bidding.
别急
Not so fast.
我怎么知道 你有能力完成这个任务？
How shall I know thy magic is sufficient to the task?
这个还不够吗？
Does thou find proof enough in this?
我相信你能做到！
That will do!
拿走！
Take it,witch!
这个足够证明了吧 我的伯爵？
Was that proof enough, my lord?
明晚来国王的城堡
Come to the king's castle tomorrow night...
并执行我的计划
and carry out my plan.
如果你失败了 你会死的很难看的
If you fail... you will be burned.
我们的英雄 当然对这些一无所知
Our hero, of course, knew none of this.
他很安全 跟着他的护卫队
He was safely in his entourage...
在去婚宴的途中
traveling, he thought, to his wedding.
这就是他 康德·瑟伯特
Here he is... the Count of Malfete.
他也是一位公爵 一位男爵和一位贵族
He is also a duke, a baron, and a lord.
一位贵族 却经常被一些小事烦恼
A nobleman, plagued by only those small things...
一位骑士的苦恼
which inconvenience a knight...
永远都得跟着 他的妹妹
the permanent presence of his sisters...
他的母亲 父亲
his mother and father...
并且跟所有的骑士一样 都得学会忍耐
and, as all knights must endure...
一个愚蠢的仆人 安德鲁
an idiot servant, Andre...
他的气味实在是难闻
whose smell made people faint...
他保持了一个记录
a considerable achievement...
从来不洗澡
among a population who never bathed.
下去 乡巴佬！
Down, peasant!
公爵 或者叫瑟伯特
The duke, or Thibault...
虽然说出于他的身份 我们不能这么称呼他
as his subjects were not allowed to call him...
十分的高兴
was joyous.
期待已久的一天
The long-awaited day of his marriage...
终于到来了
had come at last.
看看这是谁来了？
What have we got here?
又一对野蛮的皇家卫队？
Another lot of bloody royal bastards?
一定是那个法国公爵
Must be that French duke...
来娶国王的女儿
come to marry the king's daughter.
当心森林！
Mind the forest!
那有可怕的恶龙
There be dragons who'll make dinner...
它会把你当点心！
from your bones in there!
安德鲁 效忠于他的主人
Andre loved and protected his master.
主人！主人！
Master! Master!
这个森林…闹鬼！
The forest...it is haunted!
瑟伯特没有理会他
Thibault responded.
多谢 主人
Thankyou,master.
一步一步
With every step...
他越来越接近了他的爱人
he came closer to the castle of his beloved.
他希望立刻就能见到她
He hoped he would be with her soon...
但在旅程中
for rare was the journey in which Thibault...
他们其实并没有必要停下来
did not have to stop and rescue someone.
这并不是意外
This was no exception...
就象他的祖先
For like his ancestors...
他生活在一个 传统的家庭中
he lived by an ancient family rule...
那个女人在危难中！
A woman in distress!
他所知道的是
The only one he knew.
小心 主人
Beware, sire.
勇气更多于责任
Courage was more than a duty.
他坚信他的勇气
Courage was his creed.
安德鲁！快去帮你主人！
Andre! Join your master!
我在和你说话呢！快去！笨蛋！
I'm talking to you! Go, go! Stupid peasant!
主人！小心后边！
Sire! Behind you!
自然的
Naturally...
勇猛无敌！
Courage is our creed!
他是无敌的
He was invincible.
但他并不是无敌的
Except he was not invincible...
和魔法作对
against witchcraft.
这将是他最后一个胜利
For this would be his last victory...
在这一千年中
in this millennium.
下午好
Afternoon,sir.
我听说
I hear a rumor...
你明天要结婚了 我的公爵
thou art marrying tomorrow, my lord.
我也听说了
I have heard this rumor.
我还听说
I have also heard...
新娘是英格兰最漂亮的姑娘
the bride is the most beautiful in all of England.
但这并不是真的
But it is not true.
- 不是真的？ - 不是
- It is not?  - No.
难道我不是
Am I not the most beautiful bride...
英格兰最漂亮的？
in all of England?
不 等等
No. Wait.
你是最漂亮的
The most beautiful bride...
在全世界
in all the world.
戴上这个 瑟伯特
Wear this for me, Thibault.
把它和你的心放在一起
Wear it against thine heart.
你以后要老实点
Thou shalt always be true.
罗莎琳德小姐
Lady Rosalind.
别在结婚之前
Thou shalt not disgrace thyself...
想过分的事情
before the wedding.
我要去为晚宴做准备了
I must hide and dress for the banquet.
主人 你的新娘 看起来象华丽的麻雀
Sire, your bride looks like a gorgeous sparrow.
闭嘴 你这个无理的乡巴佬
Silence, you impudent peasant.
在你未来的女主人面前 要懂得尊重
Show respect to your future mistress.
是的 主人
Yes, master.
哦！谢谢 公爵
Ah! Thank you, my lord.
当心
Quite so, Your Majesty.
当我们的公主 喝了杯子中的酒
When our lady drinks her wine...
她的眼中会出现幻觉
her eyes will fill with hellish visions.
在她眼中康德将会 变成一头怪物
The count will appear as a hideous beast.
然后我的魔力将会迫使她 把她自己的丈夫杀死 哈哈哈
Then my magic will compel her to kill him. Hahaha.
各位来宾
My dear friends and noble guests.
瑟伯特 玛非特伯爵
Thibault, Count of Malfete and Papincourt...
我宣布 这个城堡将是我送给我女儿的礼物
I hereby declare this castle a wedding present.
陛下 我会尽我所能
Your Majesty, in every way that I am able...
照顾我的漂亮爱人
I will serve my beautiful lady...
并对你的王国表示尊敬
and do honor to thy kingdom.
喝完这杯 我们就是夫妻了
Drink of my cup... and you will know my thoughts.
我也是
And thou will know mine.
亲爱的？
My lord?
- 哦！ - 瑟伯特！
- Uhh!  - Thibault!
亲爱的！
My lord!
怎么了 瑟伯特？
What is it, Thibault?
这不大正常
This is not the kind of behavior...
你怎么了 儿子？
What is happening to you, my son?
你醉了？
Are you crazy? Drunk?
瑟伯特 伯爵 你别发疯了
Count Thibault, this is no way to behave...
在一个英国皇宫！
in an English court!
都是魔鬼！
Beasts from Hell!
哦！这是我妈！
Ohh! That is my mother!
瑟伯特 这是我妈！
Thibault, that is my mother!
魔鬼！
Demon!
哦 不！
Oh, no!
我都干什么了？
No! What have I done?
不是我干的 是魔力！
It is not me. It is witchcraft!
安德鲁 帮我找一个巫师！
Andre, find me a wizard!
法国会得到应有的惩罚的
France must pay for this treachery.
帮我找一个巫师！
Find me a wizard!
饶恕可怜的人吧
Have pity on a poor condemned man.
我们来进行最后的祈祷
We are here for the last rites.
主人！我们得抓紧时间
My lord! We have to hurry.
我要的巫师就是这个？
Whatwizard is this?
他是英国人 我的主人 但他的法力很高深
He's English, my lord. But his magic is very good.
是你们邪恶的沃里克伯爵干的
Your bloody Earl of Warwick did this to me.
没错
Indeed he did.
同样他也会对付我 如果他知道我在这帮你们
And he'd have me, too, if he knew that I was here.
我求你了 他可以救你
I beg you, my sire. Let him save you.
你能让我的妻子起死回生吗？
Can you bring my lady back from the dead?
我能使她的尸体复活
I can reanimate her corpse...
如果你介意
but I don't think that my lord...
她的样子或者味道
would like the way she looks... or smells.
但还有另外一个办法
There is another way.
时间就象山脉一样
Time is like a mountain.
穿梭于隧道之间
Riddled with tunnels.
我能开启时间隧道
I can open one of these tunnels for thee...
并把你带回到出事之前
and return thee to the moment before the murder.
如果你足够强壮的话
If thy will is strong enough.
你们不认为这个牧师 在里边呆太久了吗？
Don't you think this priest has had enough time?
快点
Hurry up, Father.
开门！
Unlock this door!Now!
把这个给喝下去
Drink this potion, my lord...
你将会进入时间隧道
and thou shalt descend into the Mountain of Time.
哦！好难闻
Ohh! It smells awful.
你不能喝这个
You should not drink that.
假如你变成别的怪物了呢？
What if you become a frog, or goat's feet?
你说的没错
You are right.
你先喝
Drink first, bastard.
如果你死了 我会为你报仇的
And if you die, I will avenge your death.
你们在干吗？
What are you doingin there?
开门！
Open this door!
这个闻起来象狗屎
It tastes like the shit of the pork.
他应该知道
And he should know.
每一分 每一
Per Horus et per Ra...
我忘记这个蛋了
I forgot the grouse eggs.
哦 天啊
Oh, it's a disaster.
我在时间隧道丢失了他们
I've lost them in the corridors of Time.
开门！开门！
Open this door! Open this door!
哦！好酷
Wow. Cool!
好酷啊
This is cool.
这的确很不错 仔细看！
This is pretty cool,yeah. Look at them!
看见这个农夫 躺在地板上了吗？
See the peasant sleeping on the floor?
在那个年代 人们从来不认为
In those days, people didn't think...
一个农夫该有好的待遇
that peasants deserved any better than that...
并且他们忠实于自己的主人
and they were considered the property of their masters.
看 这个农夫的主人是个骑士
Now, the boss of this peasant is the knight.
看见这个骑士漂亮的衣服了吗？
See how beautiful the knight's clothing is?
老师 他还热乎呢 刚才还喘气了！
Miss Rodett, that one is hot, and it just snorted!
那是不可能的
Now, Tammy, that's impossible...
因为它们仅仅是模型
because they're just mannequins...
模型并不会喘气
and mannequins don't snort.
但是他刚才的确动了
Well, that one just did.
不可能 他们是假的
No, because they're not real.
他们看起来就象 玩具
They're just like... dolls.
啊 见鬼！
Aaah! Oh, shit!
你在我房间干吗？
What are you doing in my chamber?
你的房间
Your chamber...
已经被劈成两半
has been cleaved in half, my lord.
这已经不是城堡了！
This is notthe castle!
什么？
What?
看这个 主人！
Oh, look at this, my sire!
这是恶魔！
It is Satanic!
这里是地狱 我们是被判有罪的人
This is Hell, and we are condemned souls.
走 我们应该找到这 阴间的王子
Come. We shall find the prince of this netherworld...
让他可怜我们
and beg his mercy.
等等 我的主人！
Wait for me, my lord!
先生 快点
Dr. Brady, come quick.
两个带着剑的人
Two guys with swords and armor...
米勒 你过于紧张了
Miller, you're always over reacting.
放松点
Now, relax.
没有必要去
There's absolutely no need to...
警察已经来了
Police are on their way.
乡巴佬
Peasant, please.
告诉我怎么走出这个城堡！
Show me the way out of this prince castle!
是的！
Yes!
- 他们好臭！ - 祝你愉快
- They stink!  - Have a nice day.
- 好运  - 等等！
- Bye. Good luck.  - Wait!
乡巴佬！等等！
Peasant! Wait! Stop!
这是什么？地狱之门！
What is this? The Gates of Hell!
看这这个火眼！
Look at its eyes of fire!
恶龙！恶龙！
Dragon! It's a red dragon!
进攻！
Attack!
你到底在干吗？
What the hell are you doing?
尝尝吧 恶魔！
Take that, beast!
我们把它干了！
We have killed it!
没错 它已经没有呼吸了
Ah,yes. It is no longer breathing.
上帝在跟我们开玩笑
God is punishing us for practicing the BlackArts.
让我们请求饶恕吧
Let us pray for forgiveness.
上帝啊 饶恕我们吧
Heavenly Father, forgive us our sins.
我们实在 实在 实在是 抱歉
We are so, so, so, so, so...so sorry.
先生？
Dr. Brady?
哦 朱丽娅 这是朱丽娅
Ah,Julia. This is Julia Malfete...
她是这次活动的发起人
who heads up the Medieval Art department.
她捐赠了这个十二世纪的古堡
She donated the famous 12th century castle exhibit.
那两个人所在的展区 也是朱丽娅策划的
Julia designed the exhibit where we found the two men.
这些是从他们身上搜到的
That stuff right there is the result of the body search.
那个大块头有金币
The big guy had the gold coins...
剑 盾牌 还有那个戒指
the sword,the shield, and that ring.
那个矮子有些腌肉
The little guy had the salt pork...
肉肠 匕首
the sausage,the dagger...
还有一颗牙骨
a molar.
还有那个盒子 我想是他偷的
And that box... which he probably stole.
应该不是从我们这偷的
Not from us.
大多数小偷都偷值钱的东西
Most thieves take valuable things.
而不是把之前的拿进来
They usually don't bring them.
这是一个歌特式的盒子
This is a Gothic pixis...
从样式看应该是 坎特伯雷出产的
the kind of design they were making in Canterbury...
在十二世纪末
at the end of the 12th century.
这上边有翡翠和红宝石
It has emeralds and rubies.
那两个人怎么会睡在那里？
Why did the two men sleep here?
他们可以去住宾馆
They could've booked a suite at the Ritz.
你确定这是从他们身上搜到的？
So, you said that you got these out of their pockets?
没错
That's right.
除了这串腊肠
Except the sausage.
这个戒指的样子看着很奇怪
This stamp ring is fantastic.
我是家族的族徽
My family's coat of arms.
能带我去见那两个小偷吗？
Sergeant, can I meet these thieves?
主人 我好饿
Master, I'm hungry.
我的肚子在咕咕叫
My tummy rumbles like a beast.
这时候你还有心情想到吃？
How can you think of food after such tragedy?
遵命
Yes.
我希望我还有机会 能再见我的爱人
What I would not give to see once more my precious...
主人！看 她还活着！
My lord! Look, she's alive!
罗莎琳德！亲爱的罗莎琳德
Rosalind. My fair Rosalind.
你还活着！罗莎琳德！
My bride. My ravishing flower.
主人！主人！
Mistress! My mistress!
你在干吗？
What are you doing?
这是一个奇迹 绝对是一个奇迹
It is amiracle. A miracle.
我认识你吗？
Do I know you?
难道你不认识我了吗？
Do you not recognize me, my lady?
我是瑟伯特伯爵
I am the Count of Malfete and Papincourt...
安德拉伯爵
the Duke of Anjou.
我是你忠实的瑟伯特啊
I am your faithful Thibault.
你说你是谁？
You're who?
我是安德鲁 伯爵的仆人
And I am Andre le Pate, valet of the count.
请饶恕我以前对你做的一切
Please, forgive me for what I did to you...
我亲爱的罗莎琳德
my dear Rosalind.
我是朱丽娅 并不是你说的罗莎琳德
My name isn't Rosalind. It's Julia.
不！你就是我的罗莎琳德
No! You are my Rosalind.
这是你给我的定情信物
The lock of hair you gave me on our wedding day.
我一直把他戴在身边
I carry it over my heart.
亲爱的 你自己自己看看吧
Please, my love, see for your self.
你也看见了？
You see?
这是盛夏中小麦的颜色
It is the color of wheat on a summer's day.
就象烛光
The color of candle light.
这就是你
It is your own.
停下！
Stop this!
- 够了！ - 罗莎琳德！
- That's enough!  - Rosalind!
你们最好先出去！
You'll be safer outside!
别离开我！
Do not leave me! Do not be afraid!
你先出去
You don't want to see this.
勇者无敌！
Courage is our creed!
别打了！我认识这个人！
Wait, stop! I know this man!
“勇者无敌”
"Courage is our creed."
这是我们家族的座右铭
That's our family motto.
这个人应该是我的表哥
This man is my cousin.
我以为他已经死了
It's in here. You see, I thought he was dead.
他在一次意外中失踪了
He disappeared when a storm...
他的船翻了
capsized his yacht during the Admiral's Cup.
人们也没有找到他的尸体
They never recovered his body...
所以当然的认为他已经死了
so, of course, declared him dead.
我是我的一个法国远房亲戚
He was a very distant French cousin of mine...
但我继承了他的遗产
but as the last living Malfete, I inherited his estate.
如果他是你的表哥
If he's your cousin...
你认为我应该怎么处置他？
what do you want me to do with him?
主人
Sire...
为什么罗莎琳德小姐 要称自己为朱丽娅
Why does Lady Rosalind call herself Julia...
并对我们受到这样的待遇 无动于衷？
and allow us to be beaten and chained?
乡巴佬
Peasant...
这不是在我们的年代
this is not our time.
巫师并没有把我们送回到过去
The wizard did not send us into the past.
他把我们送到了下一个一千年
He sent us into the next millennium.
现在已经是我之后的第十三代了
We are thirty generations removed from Malfete.
朱丽娅也不是我的爱人
Julia is not my beloved.
她是我的后代
She's my descendant.
后代？
Descendant?
我是朱丽娅
Amber, it's Julia.
能帮我接亨特吗？这件事很重要
Could you get me Hunter? It's important.
那个女人又来找你了
That rabbit of yours is on thephone again.
你好 宝贝 怎么了？
Hey, bunny. What's up?
瑟伯特 玛菲特 刚才就在博物馆
Thibault Malfete just showed up at the museum.
瑟伯特 玛菲特？
Thibault Malfete?
不可能 他应该已经
That's impossible. Isn't he supposed to be...
- 我知道  - 你能确定是他吗？
- I know.  - Are you sure it's him?
跟他的照片一模一样
He looks exactly like his photos.
他还知道家族格言
Hunter, he quoted the family motto.
他知道我们正在出售他的财产吗？
Does he know yet that we're selling his entire estate?
很难说清楚他到底知道什么
Well, it's hard to say what he knows.
他看上去很奇怪
He's a little strange.
亨特 这是不可思议的
Hunter, this is terrible.
庆幸的是他还活着
I mean, it's wonderful that he's alive...
但是可怕的是 我们已经开始出售他的财产
but it's terrible that we started to sell the estate.
哦 糟糕
Oh, God, I feel awful.
英国法庭已经宣布他死了
The English courts declared him dead.
我做这些都是合法的
We're well within our legal rights.
我们又不知道他还活着？
How were we supposed to know he was still alive?
他跟你提及钱的问题了吗？
Has he mentioned anything about money?
钱？
Money?
你在这个时候 怎么还想到钱？
How can you worry about money at a time like this?
我只是担心你
No, I'm just worrying about you.
你听起来很急躁 你的表哥现在在哪里？
You don't handle surprises well. Where is your cousin now?
他和他的朋友在楼下
He and this friend of his are downstairs with security.
今天晚上带他们回家 如何？
Why don'twe bring them home with us tonight?
毕竟还是他的家 我们是好客的
He's family after all. We want to be hospitable.
你真好
You're wonderful.
我在五分钟之后来接你
I'll pickyou all up in about five minutes.
我爱你 宝贝
Love ya. Bye, bunny.
再见
Bye, big bear.
哦 上帝 瑟伯特 玛菲特还活着
Oh, my God. Thibault Malfete's still alive.
这有点棘手
This is a disaster.
别生气
You're pouting.
不许你叫她宝贝
I hate it when you call her bunny.
哦 亲爱的 你比她强多了
You, my dear, are so much hotter than a bunny.
看看你自己 象一只母老虎
My God, look at yourself. You're a tigress.
朱丽娅 这是一件很恐怖的事情
Lady Julia, there has been a terrible mistake.
很抱歉 我们以为你已经死了
I'm so sorry. We thoughtyou were dead.
死？那个巫师只是一个笨蛋 但并不是杀手
Dead? No, the wizard was a fool, but not a killer.
他把我们送到了错误的地方
He only sent us the wrong way.
什么？
Excuse me?
我掉入了时间隧道
We fell into the Mountain of Time.
我必须回到我的时代
I must return to my time to prevent...
不然 我们的家族会有灭顶之灾的
a great tragedy to our family.
我希望你能帮助我
I ask for your assistance.
我会尽我所能
I'll do whatever I can.
太可怕了
Awful.
我们最好别出去！
We must not go out!
你在干什么？
What... what are you doing?
你们两个在干吗？我们必须在外边等
What are you doing? No, we have to wait outside.
亨特不能在这停车 我们得在外边等
Hunter can't park here. We have to wait for him.
哦 上帝
Oh, my God.
你这个胆小鬼
Bloody coward.
我们必须…
We have to...
他们消失了
Those boys are lost.
我必须去找回他们
I must go and retrieve them.
这是英国吗？
This is England?
- 不  - 肉！
- No...  - Meat!
这是在芝加哥
This is Chicago.
肉 肉 肉！
Meat, meat, meat!
这是在美国
This is the United States.
肉！
Meat!
我记得我应该在英国
The last I remember was in Sussex, England...
在我的城堡里
in my castle chambers.
你什么都记不起来了 从那以后？
You don't remember anything since then?
是的
No.
我想你可能
Do you think maybe you've suffered...
在意外中丧失了一部分记忆？
some sort of memory loss from the accident?
没错！自从我喝掉那鬼药水 我就什么都记不起来了
Yes! After I drankthe potion, I remember nothing.
- 药水？ - 一整瓶！
- Onions?  - All of them!
太好了 你喜欢吃热狗？
All right. You like to eat hot dogs, huh?
无论哪种狗我都不介意
I like to eat every kind of dog.
你疯了吗？
Now, what are you doing?
- 宝贝！ - 滚开！
- Aargh!  - Leave the dogs!
哦 不！
No, no, no. Stop it!
停手
Please, stop.
实在是对不起
I'm sorry, I'm so very sorry.
他是法国人
He's French.
看的出来
Yeah. Very.
亲爱的
Hi, honey.
情况比我想象的要糟
The situation's much worse than I thought.
你在说什么？
What are you talking about?
哦 见鬼
Holy shit.
亨特 这就是瑟伯特 玛菲特
Hunter, this is Thibault Malfete.
瑟伯特 这是我的未婚夫
Thibault, this is my fiance, Hunter.
很高兴见到你
Pleased to meet you.
- 你是贵族吗？ - 不是
- Are you noble?  - No. Sorry.
但我能确定 你肯定是
But I can certainly tell that you are.
这是安德鲁 瑟伯特的仆人
And this is Andre, Thibault's assistant.
大鼻子你好
Hello, big nose.
跟在战车后边 乡巴佬
Run behind the chariot, peasant.
遵命 主人！
Yes, master!
不能让他跟着车跑
He can't run behind the car.
因为他不是贵族 所以他不能骑
He cannot ride. He's not noble.
我知道 但他必须上车
Yes, but he has to ride in the car.
- 他很能跑  - 我们走高速
- He's very fast.  - We're taking the freeway.
- 你每小时能跑七十英里？ - 我有一双好鞋
- You can run 70 miles an hour?  - I have good boots.
不 你必须上车
No. You must sit in the car, please.
- 我能跑  - 我知道你能
- I am fast.  - I'm sure you are.
换个时候再跑给我看吧
I'd love to see you run sometime.
- 听她的吧  - 是的 主人
- Obey.  - Yes, my lord.
你要一些狗吗？
Do you want some dog?
太快了
Too fast.
你们还行吧？
Are you OK, Mr. Pate?
还是太快了！
Ohh. Too fast!
亲爱的 你能再慢一点吗？
Honey, could you slow down just a little bit?
现在时速只有二十二英里
I'm going 22 miles an hour.
我知道 你能放慢到二十一吗？
Yes, I know. Could you try going 21?
你的车怎么了？
Hey, what's the matter with you?
你知道怎么开车吗？
You don't know how to drive?
别管我
Go.
靠！
What?
马上就要到了
It's gonna be fine.
哦 上帝
Oh, dear.
别从窗户出来
Get in and open the door.
进屋吧
Let's go inside.
哦 宝贝
Hi, sweetie. Hello, Churchill.
宝贝 来这 拍一下手掌
Hello. Come here. Give Mom a high-five.
这是我的宝贝
All right. That's my boy.
走吧
Let's go.
我喜欢你的帽子
Like the hat.
安杰列！过来一下！
Angelique! I need you now!
进屋 乡巴佬
Come here, peasant.
- 马上过来！ - 我这就来
- Come now!  - OK, I'm coming.
快点
Hurry up.
你怎么办到的？
How did you do that?
黑夜
Night.
白天
Day.
黑夜 白天！
Night. Day!
在我的城堡里 没有这个发明
I do not have this invention in my castle.
你们有电吗？
You don't have power?
我有权利去判处别人死刑
I have the power to judge and condemn to death...
惩治在我领土里的坏人
any villain on my land.
哦 是吗？
Oh. Really?
亨特看来要小心了
Hunter will be so jealous.
我去给你们拿点喝的
I'm gonna get you two something to drink.
亨特从来不干这些
Make Hunter one of his power-dude smoothie things.
这个挺不错
I'd offer you one...
但除了他之外没人喜欢这个
but nobody seems to like them but him.
安德鲁 你能停一下吗？
Andre, could you please stop that?
我感觉自己在迪厅
I'm just starting to feel like I'm in a disco.
亲爱的小姐
My dear lady...
你说你会帮助我的
you said you would offer me your assistance.
是的 你需要什么？
Oh, yes. Anything. What do you need?
我要找一个巫师
I need to find a wizard.
哦！对不起 主人！对不起！
Aah! Sorry, master. Sorry!
- 对不起！ - 笨蛋
- Sorry!  - Idiot!
马上对这位小姐道歉！
Apologize to the lady!
对不起 主人 饶恕我吧
Sorry,master. I ask for mercy.
请见谅
Forgive him, milady.
没关系 反正地板也要清洗
It's OK. The floor needed to be cleaned anyway.
对了 你刚才说
So, you were saying something about what...
一个巫师？
should we say a wizard?
我要回到我的年代
I need to go back into the tunnels of Time.
当然
Of course.
我想知道在你身上 到底发生了什么
I need to just understand what has happened to you.
你的船在一次意外中沉了？
Now, your yacht went down in a storm?
不是 你听我说
No. You must listen.
我来自于过去
I am from the time of Thibault VI...
现在我来到了未来
and I have come to the future.
时间隧道 巫师
OK. Tunnels of Time. Wizards. Thibault VI.
你没事吧？
Are you OK?
没事
Yes, lady.
我看你还不相信我
Lovely flower, I see you do not believe me.
但你必须试着去接受
It is a pity, but please...try.
当然我会
Yes. Of course I'll try.
她是绿色的
She's green.
我从来没有想尝尝这个
I never really did like the taste of this.
哦 上帝 怎么了？
Oh, my God. What happened?
没什么
Nothing.
这个肉我很喜欢
I'm eating this very good meat...
还有加了沙司的蔬菜
with vegetables in a fine sauce.
明天拉屎的时候会很通畅
I will shit easy tomorrow.
这是晕车的表现
It's jet lag.
去洗手吧
All right, I'm sure you would like to wash your hands...
或者别的什么都行
and whatever else.
你跟我来？
Why don't you come with me?
就是这儿
All right. Here you go.
自己解决吧
Just gonna take this.
朱丽娅 我能跟你谈谈吗？
Julia! Can I talk to you for a moment, please?
好好使用肥皂
Don't be bashful with the soap.
那是什么 主人？一个宝座？
What is it, master? A throne?
可能是
It could be.
他们是疯子！
They're crazy!
他们的经历很复杂
They have been through a terrible ordeal.
他们有健忘症
They have amnesia.
健忘症？他们是疯子！
Amnesia? They're wacked!
他们的确很笨
They're completely retarded.
他们脑子有问题！
They're...Woo! You know?
- 清水  - 哈 哈！
- Clean water.  - Ha ha!
这个长毛巾有香味
The long towel has a good fragrance.
瑟伯特是我的表哥 他是我的家人
Thibault is my cousin, Hunter. He's my family.
是吗？我不敢肯定
Yeah? I'm not so sure.
他以为自己是贵族
He doesn't strike me as being particularly noble.
朱丽娅 下来！这有点问题
Julia, come down here! It's an emergency.
- 很好的一个泉水  - 没错
- Very good fountain.  - Yes.
你的法国亲戚在厕所里洗澡
Your French relatives are bathing in the toilet.
天啊
Oh, my God.
牙刷
Toothbrushes.
我把他们放在这
I'll just leave them right here.
我马上回来
I'll be rightback.
我要去洗个澡
I'm going to take a shower...
然后去收拾厨房
then go tackle that kitchen.
抓紧 我们的晚餐定在八点
Hurry. Our dinner reservation's at 8:00.
哦！我们去哪吃？
Oh! Where are we going?
拉图尔
Latour.
你不觉得那里有点太正式吗？
Isn't that just a little formal for our guests?
你跟我说的你表哥很高贵
First you tell me your cousin's nobility...
然后你又不满意
then you get mad at me when I suggest...
也许他并不是
that just maybe, he's not.
我选了镇上最好的餐厅 你却不高兴
Now you're upset because I pick the best restaurant in town.
我不知道怎么做 才能让你满意
You make it impossible for me to do the right thing.
没错 你是对的 拉图尔挺好
No. You're right. Latour's gonna be great.
谢谢 亲爱的
Thankyou, big bear.
- 我去洗澡了  - 好的
- I'll be in the shower.  - All right.
味道很不错
Ah. Verygood flavor.
这不是酒 乡巴佬
This is not wine, ignorant peasant.
这是洗澡用的油
It is oil for the bath.
味道很不错
Mmm. Very good perfume.
很不错
Very creamy.
轮到你了
Bathe, servant.
不 我在圣诞节时已经洗过了
No, my sire. I have taken a bath at Christmas.
- 洗！ - 不！
- Bathe!  - No, no!
我不想因为感冒而死去！
I'm afraid! I don't want to catch cold and die!
安静！
Be silent, peasant!
你还有这个洗澡用的油吗？
Do you have another bottle of this bathing oil for Andre?
你知道你刚才用的
Do you realize the bath you just took...
超过两千美元？
costover $2,000?
那是美元
That's American dollars.
很贵吗？
Is that a lot?
没错
Yes, it is.
我会还给你的
Then I will repay you with one of my swans.
哦 听起来很公平
Oh, well. That sounds fair.
我的族谱 这么多的后代
My family tree. So many descendants.
- 哪位？ - 请找卡瑟笛先生
- Hello?  - Mr. Cassidy, please.
等一会儿
Yeah. Hold on one second. Hunter?
怎么？
Yeah, bunny?
你办公室的电话 要接么？
Honey, it's your office. Do you want to take it?
- 我在楼上接吧  - 好的
- I'll take it upstairs.  - Oh, OK.
哪位？
Hello? Hello?
你好
Hello.
喂？
Hello?
你好
Hello.
你是谁？
Who is this?
我是安德鲁
I'm Andre le Pate. I have big balls...
我的屁股在冒火
and my ass breathes fire.
肯定很疼
Wow. That must hurt.
- 喂  - 喂？
- Hello.  - Hello?
我叫你别往我家打电话
I told you never to call me here.
哦 我忘了
Well, I forgot.
- 喂！ - 你跟谁在一起？
- Hello! Enter!  - Somebody there with you?
- 哦！ - 天啊！
- Aah!  - Jesus!
马上挂掉电话！否则我给警察打电话
Hangup the damn phone, or I'll call the police!
我想他挂上电话了
I think he hung up the phone.
是瑟伯特的私人助理
It was Thibault's little retarded homuncular assistant.
看 多危险
Look, this is dangerous.
我等朱丽娅睡了再给你电话？
I'll call you back after Julia goes to bed, OK?
朱丽娅小姐
Lady Julia.
你好漂亮
You are more than a rose.
你真的很漂亮
You are love's own flower.
你真好笑
Come on. That's ridiculous.
这是件旧衣服 很早以前穿过
No, I just... This old thing, I threw it on.
好几年没穿了
I haven'tworn it in a couple of years...
我应该想出一个姿势来答谢你
but I guess I should learn how to take a compliment.
多谢
Thank you.
还不够
Almost.
谢谢
Thank you.
好多了
Much better.
亲表妹的手
Kissing cousins.
我从来没有见过
I don't think that I've ever seen anyone...
一个人能吃这么多的
eat a steak in two bites before.
谢谢 主人！
Thank you, master!
祝福你！
Be blessed!
我敢保证
I can assure you...
谢谢！
Thank you!
还要松露沙司吗？
Like some more truffle sauce with that?
对不起 但是这位先生
Excuse me, butthe gentleman...
不能离开桌子进餐
can't eat off the floor.
他不是先生 他是我的仆人
He's not a gentleman. He's my servant...
他不能和我坐一起
and he's not worthy of our company.
谢谢
Thank you.
实在抱歉 安德鲁 你能
I'm truly sorry, sir. Andre, would you please...
不 夫人 这是不可能的
No, no, milady. It is not possible.
求你了
Please.
瑟伯特 能让他坐到桌子前么？
Thibault, please, will you let him sit at the table?
算我求你了？
For me?
好 我答应你
I will please you, lovely one.
来吧 你这个笨蛋
Obey,foolish wart.
谢谢
Thank you.
可他们不会感觉舒服的
And you were worried they wouldn't be comfortable.
实际上 地板更适合他
Actually, the floor wasn't such a bad place for him.
便于清洗
Easier to hose down.
奶酪！奶酪太好吃了！
Cheese! Very good cheese!
安德鲁 你在干吗？
Andre, what are you doing?
你在干吗？安德鲁？不！
What are you doing? Andre? No, no!
- 安德鲁 别这样  - 这样不好！
- Andre, no.  - No. Bad!
坐下 好好吃你的
Hey. Sit down. Eat this.
亨特 你能…
Hunter, could you...
这是点心？
No. This is for dessert. All right?
别这样
Please, sir, please.
对不起
I'm sorry. I'm terribly sorry.
都记在帐上 好吧 谢谢
Just add it to the check. All right? Thank you.
吃完正餐后再吃这个 好吗？
You eat this after dinner. All right?
没关系 真对不起
No, it's all right. I'm terribly sorry.
你只管记在帐上就行了
Just add it to the bill. Thank you.
好的
All right.
我脸上有什么东西吗？
Do I have something on my face?
你让我想起了国王的女儿
You remind me of the daughter of a king.
谢谢
Thank you.
由于血统关系
On the subject of Julia's noble ancestry...
你应该知道朱丽娅 为什么继承了你的遗产？
you do understand why she was granted control of the estate?
朱丽娅是玛菲特家族的 我的就是她的
Julia is a Malfete. Everything I have is hers.
那你没有异议 如果她继续拥有你的财产？
So you have no objection if she retains control?
- 没有  - 好的
- No.  - Wonderful.
我想你对我们的计划 会感到很满意的
I'm sure you'll be very pleased with our plans.
你将使我们…
They're going to make us...
我的意思是 你和朱丽娅都很有钱
I mean you and Julia-very wealthy.
我本来就很有钱 有成百上千的马
I am already wealthy. I own hundreds of horses...
十大箱胡椒 四百多袋羊毛
ten chests of pepper, four hundred bags of wool...
还有五十桶西班牙橄榄汁
and fifty barrels of Spanish olives.
你还有我 主人
And you own me, sire.
是的 但是你不值钱
Yes, but you have no value.
没错
That is true.
你该道歉
Excuse you.
别给恶魔留下任何东西！
Leave nothing for the devil!
- 你听到了吗？ - 是的
- Did you hear that?  - Yes, I did, sweetheart.
他们身体不大舒服
They're not in very good health, all right?
不理会就是了
So,just try to ignore it, if you can.
- 主人  - 干吗？
- Sire.  - What?
我要拉屎
I want to make pee-pee.
- 啊！你要拉屎？ - 是的
- Ah! You wantto pee?  - Yes.
去外边！
Outside!
外边？但是 主人
Outside? But, sire...
但我会被狼吃掉的
I could be eaten by the wolves.
那就找个火把
Find a torch! ldiot.
找个火把
Find a torch.
安德鲁有如此的要求 呵呵
Andre has such simple needs. I think that's great.
要帮忙吗？
Need some help, sir?
好美丽
Oh, it is beautiful.
水竟然会自己流出来！
The water comes out by itself. Ha!
这是一个有魔力的泉水
It is a magic fountain.
看这个！
Look at this! Mmm.
它的味道跟森林一样
It smells just like the forest.
这么小小的一块 就包容了整个森林的味道
All the forest is in the small wheel.
闻它！
Mmm. Smell it!
不用了 谢谢
No. No, thankyou.
你不想试一试？
You don't want to smell it?
自己慢慢享受吧
Enjoy your self.
城堡被拆了
The castle's a wreck.
所以我要帮助她分配财产
So I'm helping her divide the estate up...
使它更利于管理
into more manageable, profitable chunks.
我们要卖掉那些艺术品和高档物品
We're selling the art and various high-end pieces...
这是唯一的出路
through an outlet here.
事实上我是在帮助她 我把这视作我的责任
Essentially, I'm protecting her. I see that as my role.
土地呢？
And the land?
我也打算卖了
I decided we should sell that, too.
这由不得你决定
It is not for you to decide.
只有朱丽娅有权做出决定
Only Lady Julia can say what will be done.
我就是替朱丽娅说的
I speak for both Julia and myself.
你不能代替一个亚玛特家族的人说话
You cannot possibly speak for a Malfete.
你怎么想的 小姐？
What are your wishes, milady?
我想我还应该考虑考虑
I guess I'd like to think about it...
再考虑成熟一点
a little bit more, actually.
朱丽娅？
Julia?
你不应该打断这位小姐的话！
The lady has spoken!
鸡丁沙拉！
Chicken salad,now!
我要那个蛋糕
I want that cake. Come on now.
别全部拿走
Don't take all night.
油鸡
Greasy chicken.
你在干什么？
What on earth do you think you're doing?
你好 安德鲁
Hi, Andre.
我想我还应该在你们的帐单上
I'm afraid I'm going to have to add an order...
加上烧鸡的钱
of chicken a la umbrella to your bill.
闻闻森林的味道
Smell the forest.
很香
Yes, it's minty.
从兰色的喷泉拿的
It's from the blue fountain.
不错
Nice. Yeah. Oh, all right.
你要薄荷糖吗？
Honey, would you like a mint?
- 是  - 好的
- Yeah.  - All right. Good.
- 你呢？ - 主人
- Thibault?  - Master.
这个很不错 再给我几片
Those are good. Give me another one.
是的 很好吃
Yes. Very minty.
晚上好
Good evening, fine sir.
我在找 瑟伯特 玛菲特
I'm seeking Thibault of Malfete...
阿德拉伯爵 尊敬的骑士？
the Duke of Anjou. The great chevalier?
安德鲁不需要床
Andre does not need a bed.
只要给他一些稻草就可以了
He will be happy with some straw.
- 是的  - 我们没有稻草
- Yes.  - We're out of straw.
我的床好舒服
My bed is soft.
现在是家庭问答时间
It's time for the "Family Feud."
这些可怜的人被困在里头了！
Oh! Poor little people. They're trapped inside!
上帝 饶恕我吧 我应该怎么帮他们？
God have mercy. What are we going to do, my sire?
解救他们
Free them.
亲爱的 你真的认为他们有健忘症吗？
Bunny? You really think these guys have amnesia?
我不知道
I don't know.
我们来了！
We are coming!
你认为他们有神经病？
So you admit they're clinically insane?
我并没有那么说
I didn't say that.
哦 别这样！
Oh, come on!
他们上哪了？
Where did they go, my lord?
他们在里边 我们救不了他们
They were inside. We could not save them.
好悲哀啊
It is tragic.
反正我们也用不着这间屋子了
Well, we never really used this room anyway.
可惜
It's a pity.
我要找到巫师
I need to find a wizard now.
不介意我先喝杯咖啡吧
Do you mind if I get some coffee first?
见鬼！
Jesus Christ!
我让你别把这些东西留在那
I've told you notto leave this stuff...
居然放在路当中 你到底要干什么？
in the middle of the driveway! What are you trying to do?
你想要我的命吗！
You just about broke my god damn neck!
对不起
I'm sorry. I didn't mean to.
你到底有没有干活
Do you actually do any gardening around here...
或者你给我走人？
or do you just sing out of tune?
去弄干净
Just cleanit up!
哦！混蛋！
Oh! Hey, big belly!
你竟敢冒犯这位姑娘？
You dare to touch a lady?
你到底是谁？
Who the hell are you?
我是安德鲁 我鄙视你
I'm Andre, and I piss on you.
你最好给我滚出去
Yeah, well, you get the hell out of here...
或者我去叫警察
or I'm gonna call the cops.
对这位小姐道歉
Apologize to the lady.
小姐？你叫她小姐
Lady? You're calling her a...
好
Lady. Right.
对不起
I'm sorry.
亲她的脚
Kiss her feet.
- 什么？ - 亲她的脚！
- Do what?  - Kiss her feet!
疯了！
Oh, Jesus!
别去找巫师
Instead of a wizard...
我想我们要去看医生
I think what we really need to find you is a good doctor.
巫师是最好的医生
Wizards are the best doctors.
那在干吗？
What in the world is that?
你在干吗？
What are you doing?
快打九一一！
Call 911!
怎么了？
What is going on here?
她对这位小姐动粗
He was very rude to the lady.
看着 笨蛋 这是族徽
Look, fool. A coat of arms.
他是一个贵族
He is a nobleman.
我不知道
I did not know.
笨蛋
Stupid peasant.
- 他们是谁？ - 游客
- Who are these guys?  - Visitors.
你拥有这个女人？
Do you own this woman?
她为我工作
She works for me.
我会把他倒着吊起来的
Then I will hang my valet by his feet on your behalf.
不 主人
No, please, my lord.
吊手吧 别吊脚啊
Not by the feet! I prefer the thumbs.
我有个会要开
I got a meeting to catch.
起来 傻瓜
Rise,idiot.
我把他送给你
I give him to you for the day.
你想干吗都行
You may beat him if you like.
谢谢 但我们刚刚认识
Thanks, but we just met.
谢谢 我伟大 仁慈的主人
Thankyou, my great and merciful master.
谢谢主人！谢谢！
Thank you, milord! Thank you!
走吧 我要马上找个巫师
Letus go. We have a wizard to find.
巫师？
A wizard?
- 你是法国人吗？ - 是
- Are you French?  - Yes.
- 你喜欢这吗？ - 这很奇怪
- Do you like it here?  - It is very strange.
这味道很难闻 而且吃的东西很少
It smells bad, and the food is too little...
但有漂亮的小姐
but the ladies are wonderful.
我想我的老板也是这么想的
I wish my boss thought like that.
老板 哈哈 老板 老板是什么？
Boss. Ha ha. Boss. What is boss?
你为老板而工作 就跟你的主人一样
The guy you work for. The big guy.
我能吃他吃剩的骨头
I can have his bones when he's eating.
好恶心
That is so disgusting.
That's so gross.
你要想个办法离开他
You have to figure out a way to get away from him.
他是我的主人 我不想被吊死
He's my master. I don't want to be hung.
上吊！
Hung!
你没有必要上吊！
You're not gonna be hung!
那是违背法律的？
That's completely against the law, OK?
好
OK. OK!
他付给你很多钱吗？
Does he pay a lot of money?
每个月一次
Once every month he permits me...
允许我在他的土地上打猎
to hunt pheasants on his lands.
那就是没有钱？
So you make no money?
我有一件珠宝
I have a treasure.
你把那个叫什么？
What do you call that again?
叫“L”
The "L".
哦 等等
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
在我们下去之前
Before we get downstairs to the crowd...
我要给你这个 我家的电话号码
I've got this for you. Here's my phone number.
如果你走丢了就用这个
I want you to wear this just in case you get lost.
我不会走丢的
I will not get lost.
没有目标的人才会走丢
You can only be lost if you have no purpose...
而我有目标 我要…
and I have purpose, which is to find a...
找到一个巫师
A wizard. Right.
我都不知道应该去哪儿找
I don't even know where to start with that one.
我从来没有见过巫师
I mean, I have never met a wizard.
我不相信他们有魔力
I don't even think they make wizards anymore.
哦！我的钱包！等等 瑟伯特！
Oh! My purse! Wait, Thibault! Wait!
在这儿别动！
Wait!No!
- 把钱包那走！ - 不！不！
- Take the purse!  - No! No!
他是小偷 我要砍掉他的手
He's a thief. I have to cut his hand.
不！
No, no, no!
钱包你拿走好了
Please, just take it.
没事了
OK. Everything's fine now.
在广场把他给吊死
Hang him in the public square.
- 啊！ - 安静 老女人！
- Aah!  - Silence, old woman!
你这并不是在帮我
You're not helping.
巫师！老巫师！等等！
Witch! Old witch! Wait!
对不起 我以为你是个老女巫
I am sorry. I thought you were an old hag.
我比巫师更厉害
I've been called worse.
瑟伯特 你为什么不来告诉她
Thibault, why don't you come and tell her...
哦 不 不 不
Oh, no. Oh, no.
你见到过一个巫师吗？
Ah, would you happen to know a wizard?
能告诉我怎么找到一个巫师 啊？
Can you tell me where to find a wizard?
一个巫师
A wizard.
好的
Well.
乡巴佬 你们谁能告诉我怎么找到一个巫师？
Peasants, which one of you can show me to a wizard?
我会付报酬的
There will be a reward.
我们的兰开斯特勇士 在这找巫师
Sir Lancelot here's looking for a wizard.
我们都是？哈 哈 哈！
Aren't we all? Ha ha ha!
我不是兰开斯特
I am not Lancelot.
我是 瑟伯特 玛菲特
I am Thibault, Count of Malfete...
阿德拉男爵
Duke of Anjou, Baron of Orleans...
拉波拉的统治者
Lord of Libourne.
是吗？那我还是国王
Yeah? Well, I'm Sid from Cicero...
哈撒得的公爵 台球王子
Duke of Hazzard, Baron of Billiards...
还是
and Lord of Lord-knows-what...
现在我要和你决斗
and I challenge you to a duel.
来吧！
En garde!
别让我杀了你
Do not make me kill you.
来啊 你看见这个了吗？
En garde, I say. You watching this, honey?
因为你的傲慢 我要杀了你
I should kill you for your insolence...
但我现在太渴了
but I am too thirsty...
所以我先要喝东西
so instead, I will quench my thirst...
今天我请客
and yours and yours.
全喝光！
Drink up!
你不会相信这个的
You're not gonna believe a word of this.
猜是谁的展品
Not a word of it. Guess whose exhibit...
昨天晚上又一个访客
had another visitor last night?
东西到处在飞
There was sparks flying...
各种奇怪的声音
and all sorts of weird noises.
然后就发生怪事
Then there was this poof.
怪事
Poof.
绿色闪光 一声巨响 他就出现了
And a green flash, and then bang, he was there.
谁？
Who was there?
- 看起来象巫师  - 巫师
- The wizard- looking dude.  - Wizard.
看
Look.
他把这个床给烧了
He burnt the bed spread where he came in.
不可思议
Absolutely shocking.
等等
Wait a minute.
这个以前不在这
This wasn't here before.
他说他是朱丽娅的表哥
He says he's Julia's cousin.
我看他是假冒的
I say he's a fake.
我要在二十四小时之内得到答案
I want an answer in 24 hours.
怎么样？
See, tiger?
我将要得到这些遗产了
Daddy's gonna take care of this business.
你又会和我和好了？
You gonna be nice to me again?
喂？
Hello?
亨特 又有不可思议的事情发生
Hunter,you're not gonna believe this.
我就在这
Bunny, I'm right here.
我把瑟伯特弄丢了 因为他要找一个巫师
I lost Thibault because he was looking for a wizard.
他走丢了…
And then he just freaked out...
他丢不了的
Nobody just loses a guy...
他穿得象中世纪的骑士
dressed like a medieval knight in Chicago.
但我就是丢了
Well, I did.
等等
Wait. Hold on a second.
喂？
Hello?
有人知道
Yeah, does anybody there know...
公爵
the Count of whoop-de-do, the Baron of blah...
是的
Yes, I do.
好的 谢谢
Wonderful. Thankyou.
我找到他了 谢谢
All right, I found him. I gotta go.
- 那我就放心了  - 我爱你 再见
- I'm so relieved.  - Love you. Bye.
他又回来了 哼？
So he's back, huh?
我真希望
Yeah. I was hoping he'd tripped on his cape...
他一头掉进芝加哥河
and swan-dived into the Chicago River.
瑟伯特！
Thibault!
各位 各位！
Everybody, everybody!
这是我曾曾曾曾
This is my great, great, great, great...
曾孙女
great-granddaughter.
说真的 我的曾曾曾曾祖父和我 必须马上走
Actually, grand, grand, grand, grand, grandpa and I must go.
不行！
No!
你必须先唱一首歌！
You have to sing first!
不 我不会
No, I don't...
是的 你必须唱
Yes. You must sing first.
马上走 就现在
Have to go, now, now, now
为什么？
Why?
是啊 你应该给我们一个好的理由
Yeah. You have to give us a good reason.
我找到一个巫师
I found a wizard.
那就把他带来！
Well, bring him along!
不 我们必须走
No, we have to go.
我知道！
I knew it!
我必须走
I must leave you now.
不
Oh, no, no, no.
再见 兰开斯特勇士
So long, Lancelot.
我不是兰开斯特
I am not Lancelot.
我是瑟伯特 玛菲特公爵
I am Thibault, Count of Malfete.
我知道是那个英国巫师
Of course it is that bloody English wizard.
他也跟真我来了
He has followed me through time.
这很好 我的意思是
Great. Great. I mean, he probably...
他也刚刚喝了那东西
just whipped up some eye of new potion thingie...
并且象巫师那样
and he waved his hands over it a few times...
在嘴里说一些拉丁语！
and said some words in Latin, and voila!
瑟伯特？
Thibault?
我开始相信你了
I'm starting to believe you.
我开始相信你所说的一切
I'm starting to believe everything...
这对于一个二十一世纪的女孩来说 的确很难
and that is a really big leap for a 21st century girl.
我只是希望你能意识到这点
I just want you to appreciate that.
好吗？
OK?
他就在那
There it is.
上帝
Oh, my God.
来了
All right. What now?
- 哦  - 你这个笨蛋！
- Ohh.  - Treacherous old fool!
这是谁？
What is this?
我看见她死去了
WZARD: I thought you smote her dead.
她不是罗莎琳德
She's not my Rosalind.
我是 朱丽娅 玛菲特
I'm Julia Malfete. Hi.
哦 玛菲特家族的！
Oh. Malfete!
她是后裔！
She's a descendant!
所有的都还在
Ah! All is not lost, my lord.
你的魔法还要准备多久
How long until your magic is ready...
把我送回我的时代？
to return me to my rightful time?
在太阳下山之前
Before the sun is set.
现在去接安德鲁
Then let us go now and fetch my faithful servant.
不应该是这个味道
Never smelled like this before.
愚蠢的英国巫师
Bloody English wizards.
现在什么都干不了
They cannot do anything right.
- 我喜欢你的战车  - 谢谢
- I like your chariot.  - Thank you.
那是我的唇膏
That's my lipstick.
哦 别这样 好恶心
Ohh, no,Andre. That's so gross.
马上扔了
Hurry up. Spit it out the window.
一块红宝石
One ruby.
就是这个
That should do it.
两万五
25,000.
你们干吗？
Whatis all this horrible noise?
我们要买东西
We would love to go shopping.
哦 大天鹅！
Oh, big swans!
哦！微型战车
Oh! Very small chariots!
就像火柴盒
Like little Matchbox cars.
- 啊！ - 嘿！
- Aaagh!  - Hey!
说“CHEESE”[奶酪]
Say cheese.
我喜欢这个蛋糕
I love these wheel cakes.
我们叫它甜甜圈
ANGELIQUE: Ha! We call them doughnuts.
要多少有多少
Andre, you can have as many doughnuts as you want now.
好
Mmm. Yes.
所有这些 都可以是你的
You can have all of this, Andre.
你可以有一个大房子
You could go out and get a really big house.
一个游泳池
And you can have a swimming pool.
你能拥有所有的一切
You can have everything, Andre.
我只能拥有我主人允许的东西
I can only have what my master allows.
那不是真的！
That is not true!
这是民主国家 这是在美国
This is a democracy. This is America.
你是一个自由的人
You are a free man.
谢谢
Thank you.
这个时代 有很多有意思的东西
There are a lot of good things about living in this time.
你也可以留在这儿
You'll be OK here.
我确定
I'll make sure of it.
你很勇敢 朱丽娅
You are lionhearted, Julia...
跟你的血统一样
Like the women of your lineage.
你很有勇气
You have courage.
勇敢 不
Lionhearted. No.
不 我不这么认为
No, I don't think so.
也许吧
Bunny hearted maybe, but no.
到外边来
Come outside.
你需要懂得保护自己
You will learn to protect yourself.
你想干吗？
What are you doing?
看着我
Look at me.
照做
Take it like this.
赐予我力量吧
Power in your arm.
- 很生动  - 拿着它
- Very impressive.  - Take it.
赐予我力量吧
Power in my arm.
力量！
My arm!
我办不到 太重了
I can't do it. It's too heavy.
再来
Try again.
我受够了
I am getting so tired of this.
总要偷鸡摸狗的
Sneaking around and lying all the time.
嘿
Hey...
我们再坚持一下 就要成功了
Hang in there with me, babe. We are so close.
带我去跳舞
Take me dancing.
当心！
Hey, watchit! Ah!
对不起
I'm sorry.
你在干吗 我们走
Look what you've done. Let's go, Kelly.
快点
Come on.
对不起
Sorry about that. I'm sorry.
Sorry, ma'am.
别帮我 老板会杀了我的
Don't help me. My boss will kill me.
你是一个自由的女人
You're a free woman.
今晚就跳舞！
Tonight...we dance!
♪ I dance the rumba ♪
♪ The salsa, the cha-cha, the limbo ♪
♪ The fox trot and even the tango ♪
♪ With ladies and girlies ♪
♪ With mommies and babies ♪
♪ And DJ's gonna play this ♪
♪ 'Cause it's on their play list ♪
♪ Mambo, mambo, eh, eh ♪
♪ The babes are all around me ♪
♪ Till the break of dawn ♪
♪ Mambo, mambo, eh, eh ♪
♪ The babes are all around me ♪
亨特！
Oh, Hunter!
- 安吉利儿  - 朱丽娅在哪里？
- Angelique.  - Where's Julia?
亨特 尽情快乐吧
Hunter! Get your groovin'!
啊！
Yaah!
你是谁？
Who are you?
她是谁？
Who is she?
- 她是我妹妹  - 我不是！
- She's my sister.  - I am not!
她现在很累了 她应该回家休息了！
She's very tired now, and she's gotta go home!
亨特！
Sire Hunter!
今晚是美妙的
Tonight was so great.
最美妙的一天
Greatest night ever in the world.
你让我感觉像一个公主
You make me feel like a lady.
你就是啊 公主
But you are. A great lady.
你是我的白马王子
And you are a great man.
真的吗？
Really?
如果你把你的头发再修修
And if you got a decent haircut...
并且别把你看到的
and learned not to put everything you see...
都往嘴里塞
in your mouth...
那你会成为一个真正的王子
I think you'd be a terrific man.
我的公主 谢谢
Milady, thank you.
安德鲁
Andre...
你说我们辞掉工作如何
what do you say that we quit our lousy jobs...
去环游世界
and go travel around the world?
- 辞掉工作？ - 我们会很快乐
- Quit?  - We could be so happy.
就今天 去跟你的老板说 你要辞职？
Tonight, just tell your boss that you quit, OK?
好的
OK.
- 自由  - 自由！
- Be free.  - Free!
因为我是一个自由的男人！
Because I am a free man!
没错！
You've got that right, baby!
主人 你看上去很郁闷
Master. You are worried.
怎么了？
What is wrong?
巫师死了
The wizard...he exploded.
是的 的确很不幸
Yes. It wasn't a very pretty sight.
巫师消失了？
The wizard exploded?
我什么都不知道
Well, I don't know about you guys...
晚安
but good night.
但首先
But first...
安德鲁有话要对瑟伯特说
Andre has something to say to Thibault.
什么？
What is it, peasant?
说啊
Well, speak.
没什么
Nothing. I guess I was wrong.
瑟伯特 当他站在河边的时候
Thibault, he was standing by the river.
是我见过最美的风景
The saddest, most beautiful thing I'd ever seen.
好
Hmm. Well...
那个瑟伯特的确是一个特殊的人
that Thibault really is a special guy.
没错 他是
Yes. Yes, he is.
所以我要把所有的财产归还给他
That's why I've decided to give the entire estate back to him.
什么？
You what?
亲爱的 你知道吗 在我的家族中
Honey, did you know that the women of my lineage...
女人都是很勇敢的
are all lionhearted?
还没处理好吗？
They still haven't brought the stiff down?
我听说那个老头被分成好几部分了
I heard somebody say the old geezer's body parts...
粘在地板上
are sticking to the ground.
我要把我的身体合并回去
Best I pull myself together.
快点
Come on, my little ones.
现在舒服多了
Well,that feels better.
我能进来吗？
Can I come in?
你都查到什么了？
What do you got?
指纹对不上
Finger prints don't match.
不管你的朋友是谁 他都不是瑟伯特
Whoever your friend is, he's not this Thibault Malfete...
他已经在三年前的意外中升天了
that died in that sailing accident three years ago.
干的不错
I knew it.
我们应该马上把他送到警察局
This is how we're gonna sell it to the cops.
- 你好  - 哦
- Ah, hello.  - Oh, my...
别感到奇怪
WZARD: Well, don't look so astonished.
这就是魔法
It's magic.
我所做的只是…
All I did was cast a little...
哦 你好 我的朋友
Oh. Good day, my lord.
我真的很抱歉
I do apologize...
你这个混蛋巫师 给我进来
Damn wizard. This way.
做这个东西
The trick with pork penis...
就是要把他切碎
is to chop it very fine.
当心
Be careful.
当心 如果你碰到它
If you get that on you...
就会全身长毛
you'll grow fur.
乡巴佬！
Peasant!
准备出发
Get our things ready to go.
我们马上要回家了
Soon, we will be back in our beloved homes.
主人 我的父亲是醉鬼
Master, my father is a drunkard.
我妈是个驼背
My mother is a hunch back.
我的哥哥是个侏儒 我的姐姐是一个妓女
My brother is a dwarf, and my sister is a whore.
我已经没有牵挂
I do not have any beloved home.
我不想和你回去
I don't want to go back with you.
我再不想跟在你后边跑
I don't want any more to run behind your horse.
我要吃整个的蛋糕和甜圈
I want to eat wheel cakes and doughnuts.
我要有一辆铁制的战车
And I want to have a chariot in iron.
令人兴奋的流行服饰
And exciting men's fashions...
从欧洲的下层社会脱离出来
direct from Europe at rock-bottom prices.
我想…
And I want to...
and...and I want...
我想留在这儿 和安吉利儿在一起
and I want to stay here with Lady Angelique.
那你就走吧
There you go.
我要自由！
And I want to be free!
我要酷 我要爽！
I want to be cool and OK!
你是我的财产
You are my property.
你要和我一起回去 生死与共
You will go back with me dead or alive.
快做抉择吧
Choose quickly.
瑟伯特
Thibault...
他只是想要自由
He only wants what we all want.
他属于我
He belongs to me.
由我来决定他的命运
I decide his fate.
不 主人
No, master.
现在不是了
I mean, no way, Jose.
求你了 瑟伯特 拿出你的贵族气概来
Please, Thibault. It's the noble thing to do.
谢谢 瑟伯特
Thank you, Thibault.
祝你家族兴旺
Long life to your family.
你好 朱丽娅小姐
Yes. Lady Julia...
能帮我个忙么
If you'll allow me...
这是亨特的妹妹昨晚落下的
Sire Hunter's sister left this last night...
在酒吧里
in the house of the troubadour.
妹妹？
Sister? He d...
亨特没有妹妹
Hunter doesn't have a sister.
谢谢你 安德鲁
Thank you, Andre.
安吉利儿！
Angelique!
我来了！
I'm coming!
嘿！你是谁？
Hey! Who are you?
留在这 我帮你杀了他
Stay here. I will go kill him for you.
不 我想自己解决
No. I want to handle this myself.
你在这儿干吗？
What are you doing in here?
这是什么？
What's this?
一个来自十二世纪的英国巫师
A 12th century English wizard.
我能跟你单独谈谈吗？
Can I talk to you in the other room, please?
别碰任何东西
Don't touch anything.
这是什么？
What's this?
你玷污了女士的尊严
You offended the lady's honor.
准备受死吧
Prepare to die.
你听到了吗？他威胁我！
Did you hear that? He threatened me!
你是目击证人
And you're a witness.
你也看见了 他是一个暴徒
You see? He's a violent criminal.
还好 我叫了警察
Thank God I called the police.
你叫了警察？
You called the police?
朱丽娅 这个男人是个骗子
Julia, this man's a fraud.
他只是想骗你的钱
All he wants is the money.
不 是你想骗我的钱
No, Hunter, all you want is the money.
结束了
It's over.
什么？
What?
你不能离开我
You couldn't make it through one day without me.
算了吧
Ah, come on.
你是我的小甜心
You're my little bunny.
甜心？
Bunny?
对你来说 我是甜心吗？
Do I look like a bunny to you?
不
No.
对你来说 我是甜心吗？
Do I look like a bunny to you?
当然不是
Nay.
你知道吗 亨特？我不是甜心
You know what, Hunter? I don't look like a bunny.
我不知道如何成为甜心
I don't act like a bunny.
我也不想成为甜心
I don't think like a bunny.
如果你爱我
And if you loved me...
你就不会让我感觉像甜心
you wouldn't have made me try to feel like a bunny.
我是坚强的 我也不是笨蛋
I am strong, and I am smart...
我不需要你来照顾我
and I don't need you to take care of me.
哦 真的吗？
Oh, really?
勇者无敌
Courage is my creed.
你发疯了吗？
Are you insane?
没有
No.
收起这个东西
Put that thing away.
当然 我会的
You're right. I should.
滚出去！
And stay out!
阁下 这是不是让你想起了什么？
My lord. Remind you of anyone?
各单位注意
All units, be on the lookout...
有一个危险的男人…
for a heavily-armed dangerous male...
绑架了一名女性
with kidnap victim female.
大家小心
Use extreme caution.
这边
Go, gentlemen.
别手下留情
Don't be afraid to use your guns.
检查一下厨房
We should check the kitchen.
出租车？去博物馆
Taxi? Museum of Fine Arts, please.
快点 否则小心你的脑袋
And quickly, or off with your head.
他们逃走了！
Hey! They're getting away!
长官
Chief...
我跟着他们！
I'm going after'em!
你们从哪儿来？
Where are y'all from?
这位小姐是本地人
The lady's from here.
巫师和我来自十二世纪
The wizard and I are from the 12th century.
跟紧了
Don't lose them, O'Malley.
我们马上就来 你呆在这
We're right behind you! You stay here.
如果我们被抓
If we get caught, I will verify to the police...
我就说你是人质？
that you are a hostage, OK?
没问题 坐稳了
All right. Now we talking. Hold on.
我们能在车上回到过去吗？
Can we go backin time from here?
得在我们来的那个房间才行
We have to go through the same chamber from whence we came.
干得好
Good going, O'Malley.
疯了
Damn.
设置路障
Roadblocks established, State and Michigan.
他逃走了！
He's getting away!
我从来没有这样坐过地铁
I've never ridden the "L" quite like this before.
一个戴着头盔的人？
A big guy in a metal hat with a blonde?
哦 他们刚从这儿经过
Oh, man, they're already out of here.
空中二号
Aerial unit 2.
疑犯向南逃窜
Suspects headed south on Michigan.
疑犯进入了博物馆
Suspects entering museum.
看 骑士在家呢
Look, the knight is in his home.
欢迎你 骑士
Welcome, knight.
跟骑士说 你好
Say hello to the knight.
你好 骑士
Hello, knight.
等等
Please, wait, one second.
对不起 今天的展览暂时关闭了
I'm sorry, folks, but this exhibit is closed for today...
所以你们得离开
so you'll have to move on.
谢谢 谢谢
Thank you. Thank you.
没有你 我该怎么办？
What am I gonna do without you?
你是我的骑士
You're my knight in shining armor.
你会找到一个好男人的
Soon you will find a wonderful man to marry.
你们将百年好合
You will make a long life together.
我有感觉
I had the vision of this.
你是那么的迷人
You are so charming.
我为你感到自豪
I am so proud of you.
并且
And...
当你的孩子懂事的时候
when your children are big enough to understand...
我希望你能告诉他们 有关我的事情
I want you to tell them about an old ancestor...
因为我是你的一部分
because I am a part of you, and one day...
以后我也会成为你孩子的一部分
I will be a part of your children.
拿着
Here.
这是你奶奶的 奶奶的 奶奶 留给你的礼物
A present from your great, great, great, great-grandmother.
等等
Wait.
这个是你的
Here.
你能替我给她吗？
Will you give this to her for me?
我会的
I will.
我敢保证 她是唯一拥有
I promise she'll be the only girl...
这种东西的女孩
with anything like this.
谢谢
Thank you.
这是你的
Your Grace...
他们在干吗？
What are they doing?
很明显 他们在喝药
They're drinking vitamins, obviously.
每一个小时
Per Horus...
他在哪儿？那个穿着装甲的人？
Where is he? The guy with all the armor?
他走了
He's gone.
- 去哪了？ - 回家了
- Where?  - Home.
稍等一会儿！
One moment!
请等等
Please.
我亲爱的 沃里克伯爵
My dear Earl of Warwick...
在这欢庆的场合
in celebration of this happy occasion...
我希望你能忘记 我们之间的私人恩怨
I want to dismiss forever our disagreements.
请喝下我的酒
Please, drink of our wine.
你应该接受这和平的诚意
You shall accept this peace offering, Warwick.
我命令你
I command you.
等等！
Wait!
沃里克怎么了？
What in heaven's wrong with Warwick?
他不喜欢这个酒
He did not like the wine.
如果他不想喝 早说不就完了
If he preferred white, he should have said so.
好久没有看见你了
It has been so long since I saw you...
我们什么时候分离过？
When have we been apart, my lord?
我和朱利安在一起的时候
When I was with the Lady Julia.
朱利安
Lady Julia.
她让我把这个给你
She bade me to deliveryou this...
结婚礼物
wedding gift.
在这
Here.
有点奇怪 不是么？
It is an odd piece, isn't it?
它来自未来
It is before its time.
这就是我要说的
That's what I'm saying.
他把我从房间里扔出去
Literally, she threw me out of the house...
并且绑架了那个女人
and took off with the idiots.
禽兽不如
Animals.
他们在这里边放了什么！
They poisoned my shake!
等一会儿 等一会儿
Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
他们留下一些东西
They left some kind of note here.
一些古老的法国羊皮纸
Some old French parchment.
上边写了什么？
Well, what does it say?
我不知道 我不懂法语
I don't know, Amber. I don't speak French.
每一小时
Per Horus et per Ra...
亨特 你怎么了
Oh, my God. Hunter?
你还好吧？
Are you OK?
亨特？
Hunter?
亨特 和我说话！
Hunter, Hunter, OK, talk to me!
亨特！
Hunter!
- 别碰我！ - 啊！
- Stay away from me!  - Aah!
你们是谁？别碰我！
Who are you people? Don't touch me!
我是
I am a close and personal friend...
警察局长的好友
of the chief of police.
我就是警察局长！
I am the chief of police!
你将成为康德的仆人
You'll make a great servant for the count.
我必须告诉你 我们很高兴
I must tell you that all of us at the firm...
你没有把这个城堡卖了
are delighted with your decision to keep the estate intact.
快让我了解一下这个地方
I can't wait to get really acquainted with this place.
我们会一样一样看过来
We'll go over everything.
我甚至会带你去地牢
I can even show you the dungeon.
只要你不害怕
Unless you're afraid.
她不会害怕的
She's not afraid.
勇者无敌
Courage is her creed.
你怎么知道我的家族格言？
How do you know my family's creed?
我还知道很多关于你家族的事情
I know a lot about your family.
玛菲特小姐 他是 弗朗索瓦 拉 康博尔
Miss Malfete, this is Francois le Combier.
他是律师
He's the attorney handling the French interest...
负责处理您的法国地产
in the estate.
关于这个城堡 他比我知道的多
He knows the history of the castle even better than I do.
弗朗索瓦 你也许愿意
Francois, perhaps you would like...
当一下玛菲特小姐今天的导游？
to be Miss Malfete's guide today?
十分荣幸
It will be my pleasure.
谢谢
Merci.
♪ So let them say your hair's too long ♪
♪ Cause I don't care ♪
♪ With you I can't go wrong... ♪
我有一点担心
I have one small worry.
担心什么？
What's that?
谁来保护我远离恶魔？
Who's going to protect me from the devil?
有我啊？
You got me, don't ya?
没错！我有你
Yes! I got you, babe.
你有我
You got me, babe.
是的 我有你 宝贝！
Yeah. I got you, babe!
♪ I got you, babe ♪
♪ Your time will come ♪
♪ Have you been a fool opposed to the groove? ♪
♪ And have you been a slave to the rhythm? ♪
♪ You've been abused, forgotten, and used ♪
♪ Made quite a few bad decisions ♪
♪ Don't let this happen to you, baby ♪
♪ Look to yourself ♪
♪ See that there is no limit to what you can do ♪
♪ Get it right ♪
♪ Just keep on singing ♪
♪ La di da di da ♪
♪ The band keeps playing ♪
♪ La di da di da di da ♪
♪ Just hold your head up ♪
♪ Yeah, what's done is done ♪
♪ The hands are turning ♪
♪ I know somehow, some way ♪
♪ Your time will come ♪
♪ Your time will come, yeah ♪
♪ Lost in the silence, don't turn to violence ♪
♪ Make no mistake, there's a heaven ♪
♪ Waiting to greet you, longing to meet you ♪
♪ Don't worry, your time has come ♪
♪ I'll go the distance with you ♪
♪ Only one thing I'm asking ♪
♪ One little task that I want you to do ♪
♪ It's true, it's true, it's true, it's true, it's true ♪
♪ Just keep on singing ♪
♪ La di da di da ♪
♪ La di da ♪
♪ The band keeps playing ♪
♪ La di da di da di da ♪
♪ Again, just hold your head up ♪
♪ Yeah, what's done is done ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah ♪
♪ The hands are turning ♪
♪ I know somehow, some way ♪
♪ Your time will come ♪
♪ La di da di da ♪
♪ Some way, your time will come ♪
♪ Your time will come, yeah ♪